{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "sad",
      "description": "This deck is a TEST!",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "asd",
      "description": "asd",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "asd",
      "description": "asd",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "sad",
      "description": "sad",
      "id": 9
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "What wraps the routes?",
      "back": "<Router></Router>",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "What wraps the routes?",
      "back": "<Router></Router>",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "deckId": "3",
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf"
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "deckId": "2",
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf"
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "asd",
      "back": "asd",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "What wraps the routes?",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "What wraps the routes?",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 21
    }
  ]
}